

CONTACT ME AT

- México City
- edgarggamartgo@gmail.com
- https://edgargmartinez.com/
- @www.linkedin.com/in/edgarmartinez-g

SKILLS SUMMARY

- MEAN Stack
- MERN Stack
- React Native
- Vue.js, Vuetify, Boostrap
- Laravel PHP, MySQL, Postgres
- Django, Flask Python
- Spring Boot Java, Redis
- .NET Core 3.1 C, SQL Server, EF
- Docker
- Microservices Arquitecture
- Wordpress, Gatsby, Jest, Next
- Spoken Languages: English,
 Spanish, Portuguese and
 French

EDGAR GABRIEL MARTÍNEZ GONZÁLEZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Software Developer with over 2 years of professional experience in developing commercial web and mobile apps in both Front-End and Back-End positions, using Java, PHP and JavaScript stacks but with a keen and active interest in learning different stacks and technologies such as Django, Flask and .NET Core environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Gluo - Kohmi | July 2019 - present

- Front-End logic, UX/UI, API integration using Vue.js
- OA
- Large migration project for Posadas Corporate

Full-Stack Developer

CIAT S. de R. L. | July 2018 - present

- Front-End logic, UX/UI, API integration using Vue.js, React, Gatsby, Bootstrap and Vuetify
- RESTful API development using Laravel PHP 6.0, Node/Express, Zend, Spring boot, Postgres, MySQL, WebLogic, Apache Tomcat and MongoDB
- Small and medium scale projects for Businesses and SEMARNAT site updates.

Full-Stack Developer

Soultech | January 2019 - July 2019

- Front-End logic, UX/UI, API integration using Angular2+, Ionic
- Microservices development using Spring Boot, Oracle
- Medium scale project for SRE

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Universidad de Guadalajara UDG

Bachelor in Software Development | Jan 2020 - In process, anticipated completion December, 2022

Instituto Politécnico Nacional IPN

Completed 50% credits toward Bachelor of Mechatronics Engineering, March 2015 - August 2018.